<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.csstudio.platform.feature"
      label="CSS Platform Feature"
      version="0.9.2">

   <description url="http://css.desy.de">
      The Control System Studio defines a platform for control system
applications.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2006 Stiftung Deutsches Elektronen-Synchroton,
Member of the Helmholtz Association, (DESY), HAMBURG, GERMANY.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.desy.de/legal/license.htm">
      THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED UNDER THIS LICENSE ON AN &quot;../AS IS&quot; BASIS. 

WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. 

IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE. SHOULD THE SOFTWARE PROVE DEFECTIVE IN ANY RESPECT, THE USER ASSUMES THE COST OF ANY NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION. 

THIS DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY CONSTITUTES AN ESSENTIAL PART OF THIS LICENSE. 

NO USE OF ANY SOFTWARE IS AUTHORIZED HEREUNDER EXCEPT UNDER THIS DISCLAIMER.

DESY HAS NO OBLIGATION TO PROVIDE MAINTENANCE, SUPPORT, UPDATES, ENHANCEMENTS,  OR MODIFICATIONS.

THE FULL LICENSE SPECIFYING FOR THE SOFTWARE THE REDISTRIBUTION, MODIFICATION, USAGE AND OTHER RIGHTS AND OBLIGATIONS IS INCLUDED WITH THE DISTRIBUTION OF THIS PROJECT IN THE FILE LICENSE.HTML. IF THE LICENSE IS NOT INCLUDED YOU MAY FIND A COPY AT HTTP://WWW.DESY.DE/LEGAL/LICENSE.HTM.
   </license>

   <url>
      <discovery label="Control System Studio (CSS) Update Site" url="http://eclipse.desy.de/update"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="org.csstudio.platform"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.csstudio.platform.libs.epics"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.csstudio.platform.libs.jdbc"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.csstudio.platform.libs.jms"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.csstudio.platform.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.csstudio.startup"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.junit4"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
