<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<cheatsheet title="Plot Archived Data">
<intro href="/org.csstudio.trends.databrowser/html/databrowser.html">
<description>
The following steps show how to locate ProcessVariables in the archive
and add them to a plot.
</description>
</intro>

<item href="/org.csstudio.trends.databrowser/html/setup.html"
	  title="Open the Data Browser Perspective">
		<description>
The Data Browser Perspective offers a pre-arranged
layout of the Archive View, Data Browser Configuration panel etc.
<br/>
Select Window-&gt;Open Perspective-&gt;Data Browser in the menu bar at the
top of the workbench to access it.
<br/>
If there is no Data Browser entry, use &quot;Other..&quot;
and select it from there.
		</description>
</item>

<item title="Reset the Perspective">
<description>
You should now see a &quot;Data Browser Archives&quot; View to the left.
<br/>
If not, reset the prespective to its original state
by right-clicking on the &quot;Data Browser&quot; perspective tab
and selecting &quot;Reset&quot;.
</description>
</item>


<item title="Select Archive Server">
<description>
Select an archive data server URL from the drop-down list on top
of the &quot;Data Browser Archives&quot; View.
<br/>
One or more archives should appear. Select the ones that you
want to query.
</description>
</item>

<item
      href="/org.csstudio.trends.databrowser/html/archive_view.html"
      title="Locate Process Variables">
<description>
Enter a process variable name &quot;Pattern&quot; and press &quot;Search&quot;.
<br/>
To learn more about the available search patterns, refer to the online help via
the (?) button above.
</description>
</item>

<item
      href="/org.csstudio.trends.databrowser/html/plot_window.html"
      title="Send PVs to new Data Browser">
<description>
Select one or more PVs, right-click, select CSS-&gt;Data Browser to start
a new Data Browser instance for these PVs.
</description>
</item>

<item
      href="/org.csstudio.trends.databrowser/html/plot_window.html"
      title="Add PVs to existing Data Browser plot">
<description>
Select one or more PVs, drag them into an existing Data Browser plot.
<br/>
When dropping them on the main area of the plot, each dropped PV will
default to a new axis, which can be adjusted in the Data Browser Config View.
<br/>
When dropping them onto an existing Y-axis of the plot, the dropped PVs will
default to that axis, which can again be modified in the Data Browser Config
View.
</description>
</item>


</cheatsheet>
