<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Synoptic Display Studio - Quickstart">
  <intro>
    <description>
      Welcome to the Synoptic Display Studio (SDS) Overview. To help you evaluating the application, we provide
      some example displays that can be run with a Soft-IOC. There are 5 steps to get it running.
    </description>
  </intro>
  <item title="1. Install the example files">
    <action pluginId="org.csstudio.sds.samples" class="org.csstudio.sds.samples.internal.InstallExamplesAction"/>
    <description>
      Just click the link on the bottom and provide the name of the workspace
      project that should be created for the sample files.<br/><br/>If the link is missing here, you
      can also use the menu action under "CSS -&gt; Display".
    </description>
  </item>
  <item title="2. Download and install a Soft-IOC">
    <description>
      To run the examples you need a pre-configured EPICs Soft
      Input-Output-Controller (IOC), which should be available at http://css.desy.de.
      Please download it from there and follow the installation hints shipped with the
      IOC. Unfortunately the IOC only works on Microsoft Windows Systems.
    </description>
  </item>
  <item title="3. Launch the Soft-IOC">
    <description>
      Launch your Soft-IOC.
    </description>
  </item>
  <item title="4. Check Preference Settings">
    <description>
      Please check CSS "Preferences -&gt; CSS Applications -&gt; Display -&gt; Connection Service". To connect to channels that are provided by your Soft-IOC you
      need to choose "DAL" on this preference page.<br/><br/>
      Please do also check the EPICs settings on "Preferences -&gt; CSS Core -&gt; EPICs". If you are running a local IOC you have to add "localhost" to the "addr_list" setting.
      <br/><br/>
      If you could not install a Soft-IOC for any reason, you can give our JVM-local thread-based data simulator a try, which is independ from any IOC or
      control system stuff. It provides random double values for channel names with a "?rDouble" prefix.
    </description>
  </item>
  <item title="5. Open and Run Displays">
    <action pluginId="org.eclipse.ui.cheatsheets" class="org.eclipse.ui.internal.cheatsheets.actions.OpenPerspective" param1="org.csstudio.sds.ui.internal.workbench.SynopticDisplayStudioPerspective"/>
    <description>
      The SDS defines a workbench perspective that is optimized
      for developing displays. Select Window-&gt;Open
      "Perspective-&gt;Other-&gt;Display Development" in the menu bar at
      the top of the workbench. This step changes the perspective
      to set up the Eclipse workbench for Display development.
      <br/><br/>
      Use the workspace explorer on the the left to navigate to the
      project which contains the sample files. The file extension
      for SDS Display files is ".css-sds". <br/><br/>Doubleclicking one of the
       files in the workspace explorer will open the corresponding
      display editor. Using the display editor is straight
      forward. Further documentation will be provided soon.
      <br/><br/>
      To run a display, click the play-button in the editor´s toolbar or
      use the context menu on the workspace explorer. You can run any
      display as a view or as a separate shell.
      <br/><br/>
      A good idea is, to arrange running displays in their own named perspective.
      The perspective layout is persisted and will pop up again, when you restart the CSS.
    </description>
  </item>
</cheatsheet>
